SUMMARY

Multilingual, goal-oriented architecture graduate with over a year's worth of experience in an urban research lab and architectural offices working on schematic design, design development and construction documents (Germany: LP 2-5) for residential, educational, administration and office high-rise projects; passionate about interdisciplinary collaborations, sustainability and technology.

EXPERIENCE

Eyrich-Hertweck Architekten

09/2018 - 12/2019

Architectural assistant // Werkstudentin

Design development, construction documents (LP 2-5), interior and furniture design for multiple educational and residential projects. Prepared design analyses, space programming, visualizations, technical drawings and documentation.

Gewers & Pudewill

09/2017 - 03/2018

Architectural intern // Praktikantin

Schematic design and design development (LP 2-3) for a high-rise office for Zalando in Berlin-Ostbahnhof, residential estate with 191 apartments in Berlin-Buch, office and administration building for REWAG in Regensburg.

CHORA: Conscious City

04/2017 - 07/2017

Research tutor

Assisted in the application of code and extending a database of projects and stakeholders for an interactive urban planning tool; design of a technical booklet for it.

EDUCATION

Technische Universität Berlin

10/2017 - 04/2020

Master of Science Architecture

10/2014 - 07/2017

Bachelor of Science Architecture

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Technische Universität Berlin

Contemporary Urban Research; High-rise and engineering structures; Solar energy systems; Special areas of structural engineering; Aspects of urban planning analysis and design methodology; Data Science I: Essentials of Data Programming

Architectural Association (AA) School of Architecture

Animalesque Visiting School in Berlin

National University of Singapore

Data Science for Construction, Architecture and Engineering

SKILLS

Software

BIM | CAD

 ${\tt Revit, ArchiCAD, VectorWorks, AutoCAD, Microstation}$

Rhino + Grasshopper, Unreal Engine, SketchUp

Visualization

3dsMax + VRay, Adobe Creative Suite, Premiere Pro

Prototyping 3d printing, laser cutting

Programming

Python, HTML, CSS

Management

Microsoft Office

Languages

English (fluent), German (professional working proficiency), Polish (native)

Monika Pawlak

www.monikapawlak.com 7monika.p@gmail.com +4917640499662